nabbesh.com 2012-04-22

# Terms & conditions of use

About

Team

Careers

Contact

FAQs

Terms & Privacy

| 

Terms & Conditions 

**NABBESH TERMS AND CONDITIONS**

These Terms and Conditions of Use govern our relationship with all nabbesh Users and others who interact with nabbesh.

Access to the nabbesh Website and the use of information on the nabbesh website is subject these Terms and Conditions of Use.   
You should carefully read these Terms and Conditions of Use. By proceeding further, using or accessing nabbesh you will be deemed to have accepted them.   
By accessing, viewing, downloading or otherwise using nabbesh or any webpage or feature available through nabbesh, any information provided as part of the nabbesh services, or any related emails, newsletters or services (hereinafter collectively nabbesh or the "Services"), or by clicking "Signup with nabbesh" during the registration process, you conclude a legally binding agreement with nabbesh S.A.L (offshore), Plot number 347, unit 22, Block A, Antelias, Lebanon, based on the Terms and Conditions of Use of this nabbesh User Agreement ("Agreement") and become a nabbesh User ("User").   
Your privacy is very important to us. We designed our Privacy Policy to make important disclosures about how you can use nabbesh to share with others and how we collect and can use your content and information. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy, and to use it to help make informed decisions.   
You should read the nabbesh Terms and Conditions of Use in conjunction with the nabbesh Privacy Policy. 

**1\. DEFINITIONS**

  1. By nabbesh we mean the platform, platform features, services and search facilities we make available, including through (a) the nabbesh website at www.nabbesh.com and any other nabbesh branded or co-branded websites (including sub-domains, international versions, widgets, and mobile versions); (b) our Platform; and (c) other media, software, devices, or networks now existing or later developed. 
  2. By "Us," "We" and "Our" we mean nabbesh S.A.L (offshore). A company incorporated in Lebanon with registered offices at Plot number 347, unit 22, Block A, Antelias, Lebanon, our employees, directors and shareholders. 
  3. By "Platform" we mean the nabbesh Platform and a set of APIs and services that enable applications, developers, operators or services, including RSS feeds, to retrieve data from nabbesh or provide data to us. 
  4. By "Information" we mean facts and other information about you, including actions you take. 
  5. By "Content" we mean anything you post on nabbesh that would not be included in the definition of "information." 
  6. By "Data" we mean content and information that third parties can retrieve from nabbesh or provide to nabbesh. 
  7. By "Post" we mean post on nabbesh or otherwise make available to us (such as by using an application). 
  8. By "Use" we mean use, access, view, download, upload, copy, publicly perform or display, distribute, modify, translate, and create derivative works of. 
  9. By "Users" we mean a User(s) who is/are not registered with the nabbesh Platform and we mean a User(s) who is/are registered with the nabbesh Platform. 
  10. By "Application" we mean any application or website that uses or accesses the nabbesh Platform, as well as anything else that receives data. 
  11. By "Services" we mean searching for User Profiles on the nabbesh Platform and advertising updates and services along with nabbesh products, nabbesh software, nabbesh services and the nabbesh website. 

**2\. ACCESSIBILITY AND AVAILABILITY OF ALL USER CONTENT AND INFORMATION**

  1. We collect information in relation to Users. The information that we collect facilitates the purpose of the nabbesh Platform. Users are not required to register with the nabbesh Platform to access information on the nabbesh Platform and as such nabbesh may not have any control over how Users use the information. In order to create a User Profile on the nabbesh Platform Users are required to register with the nabbesh Platform. 
  2. When you add an application and use the nabbesh Platform, your content and information is shared with the application. We require applications to respect your privacy settings, but your agreement with that application will control how the application can use the content and information you share. 
  3. When you delete content, it is deleted in a manner similar to emptying the recycle bin on a computer. However, you understand that removed content may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time (but will not be available to others). 

**3\. REGISTRATION AND ACCOUNT SECURITY?**

nabbesh Users provide their real names and information in order to facilitate the purpose of the nabbesh Platform. Here are some commitments you make to us relating to registering and maintaining the security of your account: 

  1. You will not provide any false personal information on the nabbesh Platform, or create an account for anyone other than yourself without permission; 
  2. You will not use the nabbesh Platform if you are under the age of 14; 
  3. You will not use the nabbesh Platform if you are a convicted sex offender; 
  4. You will keep your User Profile details accurate and up-to-date; 
  5. You will not share your password, let anyone else access your account, or do anything else that might jeopardize the security of your account; 
  6. You will not transfer your account to anyone without first getting our written permission; 
  7. If you select a username for your account we reserve the right to remove or reclaim it if we believe appropriate (such as when a trademark owner complains about a username that does not closely relate to a User's actual name); 
  8. You are not a direct competitor of nabbesh; 
  9. No User may copy, transfer or use any names, photos, links, text, data or other content belonging to or posted by nabbesh or its Users for the purpose of selling, engaging in, marketing or promoting any other product or service. Illegal and/or unauthorized uses of the Website, including collecting usernames, email addresses or other personally identifiable information of registered Users by electronic or other means for the purpose of sending unsolicited email, unauthorized framing of or linking to the Website or any other use not expressly permitted in this Agreement, will be investigated and appropriate legal action will be taken, including, without limitation, civil, criminal and injunctive redress. In addition to the above restrictions, you may not authorize, enable or otherwise grant to any other person, organization, company or business access to your nabbesh User Profile or other content uploaded on the Website for the purpose of extracting such information or other content; 
  10. Each individual User Profile includes personal information about the User. 

**4\. YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH NABBESH**

  1. Your use of nabbesh products, nabbesh software, nabbesh services and the nabbesh website (referred to collectively as the "Services" in this document and excluding any services provided to you by nabbesh under a separate written agreement) is subject to the terms of a legal agreement between you and nabbesh. nabbesh means nabbesh S.A.L (offshore), registered offices at Plot number 347, unit 22, Block A, Antelias, Lebanon 
  2. Accepting the Terms and Conditions of Use?In order to use the nabbesh Platform and use the nabbesh Services, you must firstly agree to these Terms and Conditions of Use. You may not use the Services if you do not accept these Terms and Conditions of Use. 
  3. You can accept the Terms and Conditions of Use by: 
    1. clicking to accept or agree to the Terms and Conditions of Use, where this option is made available to you by nabbesh in the User interface for any Service; or 
    2. by actually using the Services. In this case, you understand and agree that nabbesh will treat your use of the Services as acceptance of the Terms and Conditions of Use from that point onwards; 
  4. You may not use the Services and may not accept the Terms and Conditions of Use if (a) you are not of legal age to form a binding contract with nabbesh, or (b) you are a person barred from receiving the Services under the laws of The Republic of Lebanon or other countries including the country in which you are resident or from which you use the Services, or (c) if you are not 12 years or older; 
  5. Before you continue, you should print off or save a local copy of the Terms and Conditions of Use for your records; 
  6. nabbesh is constantly innovating in order to provide the best possible experience for its Users. You acknowledge and agree that the form and nature of the Services which nabbesh provides may change from time to time without prior notice to you; 
  7. As part of this continuing innovation, you acknowledge and agree that nabbesh may stop (permanently or temporarily) providing the Services (or any features within the Services) to you or to Users generally at nabbesh's sole discretion, without prior notice to you. You may stop using the Services at any time. You do not need to specifically inform nabbesh when you stop using the Services; 
  8. You acknowledge and agree that if nabbesh disables access to your account, you may be prevented from accessing the Services, your account details or any files or other content which is contained in your account; 
  9. You acknowledge and agree that while nabbesh may not currently have set a fixed upper limit on the number of transmissions you may send or receive through the Services or on the amount of storage space used for the provision of any service, such fixed upper limits may be set by nabbesh at any time, at nabbesh's discretion. 

**5\. USE OF THE SERVICES BY YOU**

  1. All Users have access to all nabbesh User Profiles. Users are not required to register with nabbesh to access the information that is posted to the nabbesh website. In certain instances Users have the option to register with nabbesh. All Users agree that any registration information you give to nabbesh will always be accurate, correct and up to date. 
  2. You agree to use the nabbesh Platform only for purposes that are permitted by (a) the Terms and Conditions of Use and (b) any applicable law, regulation or generally accepted practices or guidelines in the relevant jurisdictions (including any laws regarding the export of data or software to and from Lebanon or other relevant countries). 
  3. You agree not to access (or attempt to access) any of the Services by any means other than through the interface that is provided by nabbesh. 
  4. You agree that you will not engage in any activity that interferes with or disrupts the Services (or the servers and networks which are connected to the Services). 
  5. You agree that you will not reproduce, duplicate, copy, sell, trade or resell any of the information on the nabbesh Platform for any purpose. 
  6. You agree that you are solely responsible for (and that nabbesh has no responsibility to you or to any third party for) any breach of your obligations under the Terms and Conditions of Use and for the consequences (including any loss or damage which nabbesh may suffer) of any such breach. 
  7. You agree that you will not send or otherwise post unauthorized commercial communications (such as spam) on the nabbesh Platform. 
  8. You will not collect Users' content or information, or otherwise access the nabbesh Platform, using automated means (such as harvesting bots, robots, spiders, or scrapers) without our permission. 
  9. You will not engage in unlawful multi-level marketing, such as a pyramid scheme, on the nabbesh Platform. 
  10. You will not upload viruses or other malicious code. 
  11. You will not solicit login information or access an account belonging to someone else. 
  12. You will not bully, intimidate, or harass any User. 
  13. You will not post content that is hateful, libellous, slanderous, defaming, threatening, pornographic, or that contains nudity or graphic or gratuitous violence. 
  14. You will not develop or operate a third party application containing or advertise or otherwise market alcohol-related or other mature content without appropriate age-based restrictions. 
  15. You will not offer any contest, giveaway, or sweepstakes ("promotion") on nabbesh without our prior written consent. If we consent, you take full responsibility for the promotion, and will follow our Promotions Guidelines and all applicable laws. 
  16. You will not use the nabbesh Platform to do anything unlawful, misleading, malicious, or discriminatory. 
  17. You will not do anything that could disable, overburden, or impair the proper working of the nabbesh Platform, such as a denial of service attack. 
  18. You will not facilitate or encourage any violations of this Statement 

**6\. YOUR PASSWORDS AND ACCOUNT SECURITY**

  1. You agree and understand that you are responsible for maintaining the confidentiality of passwords associated with your User account registration to use to access your User Profile. 
  2. Accordingly, you agree that you will be solely responsible to nabbesh for all activities that occur under your account. 
  3. If you become aware of any unauthorised use of your password or of your account, you agree to notify nabbesh immediately. 
  4. Login details - nabbesh will store the User's access details so that when a registered User logs in and accesses the nabbesh Platform nabbesh may offer the User the option to sync their contacts. nabbesh will ask the User to consent to having their contacts synced. 
  5. nabbesh reserves the right to remove, edit, move or close any account for any reason and to suspend or ban any User account for any reason. 
  6. You understand that all information (such as data files, written text, computer software, music, audio files or other sounds, photographs, videos or other images) which you may have access to as part of, or through your use of, the Services are the sole responsibility of the person from which such content originated. All such information is referred to above as the "Content". 
  7. You should be aware that Content presented to you as part of the nabbesh search facility, including but not limited to User Profiles, advertisements in the Services and sponsored Content within the Services may be protected by intellectual property rights which are owned by the sponsors or advertisers who provide that Content to nabbesh (or by other persons or companies on their behalf). You may not modify, rent, lease, loan, sell, distribute or create derivative works based on this Content (either in whole or in part) unless you have been specifically told that you may do so by nabbesh or by the owners of that Content, in a separate agreement. 
  8. nabbesh reserves the right (but shall have no obligation) to pre-screen, review, flag, filter, modify, refuse or remove any or all Content from any Service. For some of the Services, nabbesh may provide tools to filter out explicit sexual content. There are commercially available services and software to limit access to material that you may find objectionable. 
  9. 1You understand that by using the nabbesh Platform you may be exposed to Content that you may find offensive, indecent or objectionable and that, in this respect, you use the nabbesh Platform at your own risk. 
  10. You agree that you are solely responsible for (and that nabbesh has no responsibility to you or to any third party for) any Content that you create, transmit or display while using the nabbesh Platform and for the consequences of your actions (including any loss or damage which nabbesh may suffer) by doing so. 

**7\. OTHER PEOPLE'S RIGHTS**

  1. We respect other people's rights, and expect you to do the same. 
  2. You will not post content or take any action on the nabbesh Platform that infringes or violates someone else's rights or otherwise violates the law. 
  3. nabbesh can remove any content or information you post on the nabbesh Platform if we believe that it violates this Statement. 
  4. If you repeatedly infringe other people's intellectual property rights, we will disable your account when appropriate. 
  5. You will not use our copyrights or trademarks (including nabbesh, the nabbesh Logos) or any confusingly similar marks, without our written permission. 
  6. If you collect information from Users, you will: obtain their consent, make it clear you (and not nabbesh) are the one collecting their information, and post a privacy policy explaining what information you collect and how you will use it. 
  7. You will not post anyone's identification documents or sensitive financial information on the nabbesh Platform. 

**8\. PROPRIETARY RIGHTS**

  1. You acknowledge and agree that nabbesh owns all legal right, title and interest in and to the nabbesh Platform, including any intellectual property rights which subsist in the nabbesh Platform (whether those rights happen to be registered or not, and wherever in the world those rights may exist). 
  2. You agree that nothing in the Terms and Conditions of Use gives you a right to use any of nabbesh's trade names, trademarks, service marks, logos, domain names, and other distinctive brand features. 
  3. nabbesh acknowledges and agrees that it obtains no right, title or interest from you (or your licensors) under these Terms and Conditions of Use in or to any Content that you submit, post, transmit or display on, or through, the Services, including any intellectual property rights which subsist in that Content (whether those rights happen to be registered or not, and wherever in the world those rights may exist). You agree that you are responsible for protecting and enforcing those rights and that nabbesh has no obligation to do so on your behalf. 
  4. You agree that you shall not remove, obscure, or alter any proprietary rights notices (including copyright and trademark notices) which may be affixed to or contained within the nabbesh Platform. 
  5. You agree that in using the nabbesh Platform, you will not use any trademark, service mark, trade name, logo of any company or organisation in a way that is likely or intended to cause confusion about the owner or authorised User of such marks, names or logos. 

**9\. PROHIBITED CONTENT?**

This Section enumerates a non-exhaustive list of content you may in any event not make available via nabbesh (it being at the sole discretion of nabbesh to decide whether certain content is or is not permitted): 

  1. Content which is discriminatory as to appearance, race, religion, gender, culture, origin or which can otherwise be called offensive; 
  2. Content which incites to violence against and/or harassment of another person or other persons; 
  3. Content which leads to or is the result of exploitation or abuse of others; 
  4. Content which according to nabbesh is contrary to public morality or good taste, is violent or includes a link to pornographic material or pornographic websites, or includes pornographic or erotic material; 
  5. Content which asks for personal data of minors and/or makes available personal data of other persons; 
  6. Content which encourages or commits the performance of illegal activities; 
  7. Content which infringes intellectual property rights, privacy rights or any other rights of nabbesh or third parties; 
  8. Content which involves chain letters, junk mail or spamming and/or which asks for passwords or other information leading back to persons for commercial or illegal purposes; 
  9. Content which, without the prior written consent of nabbesh, involves commercial activity such as advertising, lotteries, contests or pyramid games; 
  10. Content which includes a photograph or likeness of another person without that person's consent; 
  11. Content which infringes any law, regulation, bye-law, other applicable regulations or these Terms and Conditions of Use. 

**10\. PAYMENTS?**

If you make a payment on the nabbesh site or the nabbesh Platform you agree to our Payments Terms. 

**11\. LICENCE FROM nabbesh**

  1. nabbesh gives you a personal, worldwide, royalty-free, non-assignable and non-exclusive licence to use the software provided to you by nabbesh as part of the Services as provided to you by nabbesh. This licence is for the sole purpose of enabling you to use and enjoy the benefit of the Services as provided by nabbesh, in the manner permitted by the Terms and Conditions of Use. 
  2. You may not (and you may not permit anyone else to) copy, modify, create a derivative work of, reverse engineer, decompile or otherwise attempt to extract the source code of the Software or any part thereof. 
  3. You may not assign (or grant a sub-licence of) your rights to use the Software, grant a security interest in or over your rights to use the Software, or otherwise transfer any part of your rights to use the Software. 

**12\. CONTENT LICENCE FROM YOU**

  1. You retain copyright and any other rights you already hold in Content which you submit, post or display on or through, the nabbesh Platform. By submitting, posting or displaying the Content you give nabbesh a perpetual, irrevocable, worldwide, royalty-free, and non-exclusive licence to reproduce, adapt, modify, translate, publish, publicly perform, publicly display and distribute any Content which you submit, post or display on or through, the nabbesh Platform. This licence is for the sole purpose of enabling nabbesh to display, distribute and promote the nabbesh Platform. 
  2. You agree that this licence includes a right for nabbesh to make such Content available to all. 
  3. You understand that nabbesh, in performing the required technical steps to provide the nabbesh Platform services to our Users, may (a) transmit or distribute your Content over various public networks and in various media; and (b) make such changes to your Content as are necessary to conform and adapt that Content to the technical requirements of connecting networks, devices, services or media. You agree that this licence shall permit nabbesh to take these actions. 
  4. You confirm and warrant to nabbesh that you have all the rights, power and authority necessary to grant the above licence. 

**13\. SOFTWARE UPDATES?**

The Software which you use may automatically download and install updates from time to time from nabbesh. These updates are designed to improve, enhance and further develop the nabbesh Platform and the nabbesh Platform Services and may take the form of bug fixes, enhanced functions, new software modules and completely new versions. You agree to receive such updates (and permit nabbesh to deliver these to you) as part of your use of the nabbesh Platform and the nabbesh Platform Services. 

**14\. ENDING YOUR RELATIONSHIP WITH NABBESH**

  1. The Terms and Conditions of Use will continue to apply until terminated by either you or nabbesh as set out below. 
  2. If you want to terminate your legal agreement with nabbesh, you may do so by (a) notifying nabbesh at any time; and (b) deleting your User Profile from the nabbesh Platform. 
  3. nabbesh may at any time, terminate its legal agreement with you if: 
    1. You have breached any provision of the Terms and Conditions of Use (or have acted in a manner which clearly shows that you do not intend to, or are unable to comply with the provisions of the Terms and Conditions of Use); or 
    2. nabbesh is required to do so by law (for example, where the provision of User Profile services is, or becomes, unlawful); or 
    3. nabbesh is transitioning to no longer providing the nabbesh Platform and nabbesh Platform Services to Users in the country in which you are resident or from which you use the service; or 
    4. The provision of the nabbesh Platform or nabbesh Platform Services to you by nabbesh is, in nabbesh's opinion, no longer commercially viable; 
    5. When these Terms and Conditions of Use come to an end, all of the legal rights, obligations and liabilities that you and nabbesh have benefited from, been subject to (or which have accrued over time whilst the Terms and Conditions of Use have been in force) or which are expressed to continue indefinitely, shall be unaffected by this cessation, and the provisions of paragraph 1.14.6 shall also continue to apply to such rights, obligations and liabilities indefinitely. 
  4. If you deactivate your account Users will not be able to see it but it will not be deleted. Your User Profile information will be saved in the event that you wish to reinstate your User Profile information. When you delete your account however, it is permanently deleted. You will not be able to reinstate your User Profile, you will have to create a new User Profile. 
  5. Even after you deactivate or delete your User Profile you should be aware that copies of the information may remain accessible elsewhere, specifically in relation to the extent that it has been previously shared with others, or it was copied or stored by other Users. 
  6. Removed and deleted information may persist in backup copies for a reasonable period of time (but will not be available to others). 

**15\. EXCLUSION OF WARRANTIES**

  1. Access to the nabbesh Platform is provided "as is" and nabbesh gives you no warranty with respect to them. 
  2. In particular, nabbesh does not represent or warrant to you that: 
    1. your use of the nabbesh Platform will meet your requirements; 
    2. your use of the nabbesh Platform will be uninterrupted, timely, secure or free from error; 
    3. any information obtained by you as a result of your use of the nabbesh Platform will be accurate or reliable; and 
    4. that defects in the operation or functionality of any Software provided to you as part of the nabbesh Platform will be corrected. 
  3. No conditions, warranties or other terms (including any implied terms as to satisfactory quality, fitness for purpose or conformance with description) apply to the nabbesh Platform except to the extent that they are expressly set out in the Terms and Conditions of Use. 
  4. Nothing in the Terms and Conditions of Use shall affect those statutory rights which you are always entitled to as a consumer and that you cannot contractually agree to alter or waive. 

**16\. LIMITATION OF LIABILITY**

  1. Nothing in these Terms and Conditions of Use shall exclude or limit nabbesh's liability for losses which may not be lawfully excluded or limited by applicable law. 
  2. Subject to overall provision in paragraph 1.16.1 above, nabbesh shall not be liable to you for: 
    1. any indirect or consequential losses which may be incurred by you. This shall include any loss of profit (whether incurred directly or indirectly), any loss of goodwill or business reputation, or any loss of data suffered by you; 
    2. any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result of: 
    3. any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, or as a result of any relationship or transaction between you and any advertiser or sponsor whose advertising appears on the nabbesh Platform; 
    4. any changes which nabbesh may make to the nabbesh Platform or nabbesh Services, or for any permanent or temporary cessation in the provision of the nabbesh Platform or nabbesh Services, (or any features within the nabbesh Platform or nabbesh Services); 
    5. the deletion of, corruption of, or failure to store, any Content and other communications data maintained or transmitted by or through your use of the nabbesh Platform or nabbesh Services; 
    6. your failure to provide nabbesh with accurate account information; 
    7. your failure to keep your password or account details secure and confidential. 
  3. The limitations on nabbesh's liability to you in paragraph 1.16.2 above shall apply whether or not nabbesh has been advised of or should have been aware of the possibility of any such losses arising. 

**17\. ADVERTISEMENTS**

  1. Some of the nabbesh Services are supported by advertising revenue and may display advertisements and promotions. These advertisements may be targeted to the content of information stored on the nabbesh Platform, queries made through the nabbesh Platform or other information. 
  2. The manner, mode and extent of advertising by nabbesh on the nabbesh Platform and in relation to the nabbesh Services are subject to change without specific notice to you. 
  3. In consideration for nabbesh granting you access to and use of the nabbesh Platform, you agree that nabbesh may place such advertising on the nabbesh Platform. 

**18\. ADVERTISMENTS ON nabbesh?**

Our goal is to deliver ads that are not only valuable to advertisers, but also valuable to you. In order to do that, you agree to the following: 

  1. That nabbesh may use your personal information to assist us in serving sponsored content on your User Profile or elsewhere. You give us permission to use your name and User Profile photo in connection with that content; 
  2. We do not give your content or information to advertisers without your consent; 
  3. You understand that we may not always identify paid services and communications as such. 

**19\. OTHER CONTENT**

  1. The nabbesh Platform may include hyperlinks to other websites or content or resources. nabbesh may have no control over any websites or resources which are provided by companies or persons other than nabbesh. 
  2. You acknowledge and agree that nabbesh is not responsible for the availability of any such external sites or resources, and does not endorse any advertising, products or other materials on or available from such websites or resources. 
  3. You acknowledge and agree that nabbesh is not liable for any loss or damage which may be incurred by you as a result of the availability of those external sites or resources, or as a result of any reliance placed by you on the completeness, accuracy or existence of any advertising, products or other materials on, or available from, such websites or resources. 

**20\. CHANGES TO THE TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE**

  1. nabbesh may make changes to the Terms and Conditions of Use from time to time. When these changes are made, nabbesh will make a new copy of the Terms and Conditions of Use available to you from within, or through, the nabbesh Platform and nabbesh Services. 
  2. You understand and agree that if you use the nabbesh Platform or nabbesh Services after the date on which the Terms and Conditions of Use or Additional Terms and Conditions of Use have changed, nabbesh will treat your use as acceptance of the updated Terms and Conditions or Use or Additional Terms and Conditions of Use. 

**21\. GENERAL LEGAL TERMS**

  1. Sometimes when you use the nabbesh Platform, you may (as a result of, or through your use of the nabbesh Platform) use a service or download a piece of software, or purchase goods, which are provided by another person or company. Your use of these other services, software or goods may be subject to separate terms between you and the company or person concerned. If so, the Terms and Conditions of Use do not affect your legal relationship with these other companies or individuals. 
  2. The Terms and Conditions of Use govern your use of the nabbesh Platform and nabbesh Services and completely replace any prior Terms and Conditions of Use between you and nabbesh in relation to the nabbesh Platform and nabbesh Services. 
  3. You agree that nabbesh may provide you with notices, including those regarding changes to the Terms and Conditions of Use, by email, regular mail, or postings on the nabbesh Platform. 
  4. You agree that if nabbesh does not exercise or enforce any legal right or remedy which is contained in the Terms and Conditions of Use (or which nabbesh has the benefit of under any applicable law), this will not be taken to be a formal waiver of nabbesh's rights and that those rights or remedies will still be available to nabbesh. 
  5. If any court of law, having the jurisdiction to decide on this matter, rules that any provision of these Terms and Conditions of Use is invalid, then that provision will be removed from the Terms and Conditions of Use without affecting the rest of the Terms and Conditions of Use. The remaining provisions of the Terms and Conditions of Use will continue to be valid and enforceable. 
  6. The Terms and Conditions of Use, and your relationship with nabbesh under the Terms and Conditions of Use, shall be governed by Lebanese law. You and nabbesh agree to submit to the exclusive jurisdiction of the courts of The Republic of Lebanon to resolve any legal matter arising from the Terms and Conditions of Use. Notwithstanding this, you agree that nabbesh shall still be allowed to apply for injunctive remedies (or an equivalent type of urgent legal relief) in any jurisdiction. 

**22\. PRIVACY**

  1. General Statement ?  
Your privacy is very important to us. Our Privacy Policy has been designed to reflect our commitment to ensuring the privacy of your information. The nabbesh Privacy Policy makes important disclosures about how you can use nabbesh to share your User Profile information with all Users of the nabbesh Platform and how we in turn collect and can use your content and information. We encourage you to read the Privacy Policy and to use it to help you, the User, make informed decisions. We will only collect, store and use your personal information for defined purposes which are outlined in our Privacy Policy and our Data Protection Policy. We use your information to provide you with our service, to support and enhance our relationship with you, for example, to provide service and support, and share product, services and nabbesh news and offerings with you. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. ?Periodically, we may send you information about nabbesh products and services we feel may be of interest to you. ?We have no desire or intent to infringe on your privacy while using our site. See our Data Protection Policy for full information on collection and use of personal information. ?We understand that as a registered User of the nabbesh Platform the privacy and the security of your information is very important to you. The purpose of our Privacy Statement is to outline nabbesh's practices in this area. 
  2. Changes to the Privacy Policy ?  
Please note that this Privacy Policy may change from time to time. We will not reduce your rights under this Privacy Policy without your explicit consent and we expect that the majority of such changes will be minor. Regardless, we will post any Privacy Policy changes on the nabbesh website and, if the changes are significant, we will provide a more prominent notice (including, for certain services, email notification of Privacy Policy changes). ?PLEASE NOTE that this Privacy Statement is subject to the Terms and Conditions of Use of the nabbesh Website. We recommend that you read the Terms and Conditions of Use. If there is a conflict between the Terms and Conditions of Use and this Privacy Statement, the Terms and Conditions of Use shall prevail. Except as otherwise provided, terms used herein and defined in the Terms and Conditions of Use shall have the same meaning that is given to them in the Terms and Conditions of Use. 

**23\. DATA PROTECTION POLICY**

  1. PROVIDING THE SERVICE FOR WHICH YOU HAVE APPLIED The information collected by nabbesh is used to facilitate the operation of the nabbesh Platform. 
  2. KEEPING YOU INFORMED   
There may be times when we feel that a service or product offered by us or a selected third party may benefit you. We may use information we obtain from your account transactions and your User Profile in this decision-making process. To make you aware of the service or product we may contact you by mail or other methods provided from your User Profile information to give you further details so that you can make an informed choice. 
  3. RESEARCH & STATISTICAL ANALYSIS   
We will use your details to assist us in understanding individual needs and business trends in order to improve the nabbesh products and services we offer. 
  4. EMAIL/SMS   
If you email us, or give us your email address or SMS number, we will keep a record of it. With your explicit consent, we may use it to contact you occasionally about other nabbesh products and services which may interest you. We will not give your email address or SMS number to any unauthorised third parties. When emailing us, always use the email facility on the nabbesh website to make sure that the content of your email is secure. If you send us email in other ways, remember that it will be insecure and could be intercepted. If you do send us insecure email, please keep the amount of confidential information you include to a minimum. 
  5. THE INFORMATION WE COLLECT   
As you browse through our Website, our web server collects information about your visit, not about you personally. This information is anonymous and no attempt is or will be made to identify visitors. ?All information provided to us by you will be treated with the utmost confidentiality in accordance with all applicable legislative and regulatory standards. nabbesh will remove or amend the information as appropriate in accordance with applicable legislative and regulatory requirements. 
  6. USE OF 'COOKIES' 
    1. What is a cookie? Cookies are small pieces of information, stored in simple text files, placed on your computer by a website. Cookies can be read by the website on your subsequent visits. The information stored in a cookie may relate to your browsing habits on the web page, or a unique identification number so that the website can "remember" you on your return visit. Generally speaking, cookies do not contain personal information from which you can be identified, unless you have furnished such information to the website in your User Profile. 
    2. How does nabbesh use cookies? When you visit nabbesh, we collect your browser type and IP address. This information is gathered for all nabbesh Users. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using 'cookies'. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the User's computer tied to information about the User. We send cookies to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use session ID cookies to confirm that Users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the User closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to nabbesh. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. We use cookies to collect information about visitors' use of the nabbesh website. The information collected by cookies enables nabbesh to understand the use of its site. This in turn helps to provide visitors with a better experience. nabbesh will not attempt to personally identify visitors from their IP addresses. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service. nabbesh also uses cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web. We may set one or more cookies in your browser when you visit a website, including nabbesh sites that use our advertising cookies and that view or click an ad supported by nabbesh's advertising services. ?Cookies will not be used to contact you for marketing purposes other than by means of advertisements offered within the nabbesh website. Cookies do not in any way compromise the security of your computer. 
    3. Retention. We will retain your data for as long as you have a User Profile on the nabbesh Platform. If you wish to remove your User Profile information you must delete the User Profile by going to your User Account Settings. 
    4. Consent. By providing nabbesh with your information and by your use of this Website you consent to all of your information being used, accessible, available processed, disclosed and retained as set out above. 
    5. Representation. By your use of this Website you warrant and represent to us that in respect of any personal data of any data subject which you provide to us, you have the authority of that data subject to disclose such data to us on these Terms and Conditions of Use and for all the purposes herein set out and to give the consents set out above on behalf of each such data subject, and accordingly, all references in these documents to you shall be deemed to include any such data subject. 
    6. Confidentiality & Disclosure of information. Outside of the nabbesh Platform we will treat all your personal information as private and confidential (even when you are no longer a nabbesh User). Nothing about your accounts (apart from what you upload to your User Profile) will be disclosed to anyone, other than in the exceptional cases permitted by law. These include: 
      1. where we are legally compelled to do so; 
      2. where there is a duty to the public to disclose; 
      3. where disclosure is required to protect our interests (this will not be used as a reason for disclosing information about you or your information, including your name and address, to anyone else for marketing purposes); 
      4. where disclosure is made at your request or with your consent; 
      5. where disclosure is necessary for the performance of our legal agreements with you. 
  
From time to time we may employ agents and sub-contractors to process your information on our behalf to ensure that your online transactions are secure. The same duty of confidentiality and security will apply to our agents and sub-contractors and all processing will only be carried out under our instruction and will be supported by written contract. In instances where your information may also be shared by contracted third parties these third parties will similarly be under the same duty of confidentiality and security in respect of your data. nabbesh will not divulge customer information to a third party unless we have received customer authorisation or we are required to do so by law or you have selected to do so on your User Profile. 
  7. SECURITY OF INFORMATION  
At nabbesh, we understand how important the security and confidentiality of your information is to you. Keeping customer information secure is a top priority for nabbesh. ?Even so, nabbesh S.A.L (offshore) cannot and does not guarantee the privacy or confidentiality of information relating to you that passes over the Internet. In accessing this Website and in availing of any of the services/information available on or via this Website, you are deemed by the Terms and Conditions of Use to accept that electronic mail messaging and Internet communication may not be free from interference by third parties and may not remain confidential. ?In all circumstances the use by you of this Website is at your sole risk.?You are solely responsible for maintaining your User Profile information. Please be careful and responsible whenever you are online. While we strive to protect your personal information, we cannot ensure or warrant that it will be at all times secure from unauthorised use and you transmit to us at your own risk. You can be assured that we have taken the necessary steps to protect your information by using some of the latest technologies available. This enables you to transact with us online in confidence. 
  8. DATA ENCRYPTION   
To help protect your credit card number and personal information, we encrypt transactions where necessary. 
  9. HYPERLINKS   
Some of the pages on this Website contain hyperlinks to websites not maintained by nabbesh. You are reminded that different Terms and Conditions of Use will apply to you as a User of such websites. In addition such websites may not attain the same privacy standards that nabbesh maintains. 
  10. AMENDMENTS  
The contents of this Website, including these Terms and Conditions of Use, any information contained on this Website and our Privacy Statement are subject to change and to being updated without notice from time to time. 
  11. ATTEMPTED USE OF WEBSITE   
The nabbesh Terms and Conditions of Use shall also apply, subject to alteration as necessary, to attempted access of the Website and attempted use of information on it. 
  12. GENERAL 
    1. In the event that any provision in the nabbesh Terms and Conditions of Use is held to be unenforceable or invalid, such provision shall be severed and the remaining provisions shall be enforceable to the fullest extent permitted by the laws of Lebanon. 
    2. Clause headings in the nabbesh Terms and Conditions of Use are for reference purposes only and shall not be used to construe or determine the meaning of any or all of the nabbesh Terms and Conditions of Use. 

**24\. SALE OF BUSINESS?**

We reserve the right to transfer information (including your personal information) to a third party in the event of a sale, merger, liquidation, receivership or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of our company. 

**25\. SECURITY?**

Your personal information is held on secure servers hosted by our Internet Service Provider. Unfortunately, no data transmission over the Internet can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. As a result, while we will take all reasonable steps to protect your personal information, the nature of the Internet is such that we cannot and do not guarantee or warrant the security of any information you transmit to us via the Internet. 

**26\. GOVERNING LAW AND JURISDICTION?**

Information appearing on this Website is provided in accordance with and subject to the laws of The Republic of Lebanon and the laws of The Republic of Lebanon govern the conduct and operation of the nabbesh website. The courts of The Republic of Lebanon have exclusive jurisdiction over all claims or disputes arising in relation to, out of, or in connection with these Terms and Conditions of Use, the information contained on this Website, and any use made of that information. Any such claims or disputes shall be resolved in accordance with the laws of the Republic of Lebanon. 

**27\. DISCLAIMER AS TO ACCURACY OF INFORMATION?**

Care has been taken in the preparation of the information contained on this Website. However, we do not make any representations or warranties as to the accuracy of the information contained on this Website. 

**28\. PROHIBITED USE OF WEBSITE?**

The information on this Website is not intended to be provided to and should not be used in any jurisdiction of any nature in which access to or use of such information is prohibited, whether in the format in which it is presented on this Website or otherwise. If you have any doubts about the legality of your using this Website, you should not continue any further. 

**29\. GENERAL DISCLAIMER OF LIABILITY?**

No member of nabbesh S.A.L (offshore) (or any other person involved with the provision and maintenance of the nabbesh website) takes any responsibility for the accuracy of the information provided on the nabbesh website. Use of such information is at the User's sole risk. No member of nabbesh S.A.L (offshore) accepts any liability for any loss or damage of any nature, including but not limited to loss of profits, goodwill, or any other type of financial or other pecuniary or direct or special indirect or consequential loss howsoever arising whether in negligence or for breach of contract or other duty as a result of: 

  1. use of this Website, including but not limited to any electronic mail messaging and Internet communication that may arise from, in the course of or pursuant to such use; and/or 
  2. reliance on the information contained in this Website, whether: 
    1. downloaded or not; 
    2. authorized or not. 
  
nabbesh S.A.L (offshore) makes no representation or warranty or undertaking of any kind in relation to the analysis or information contained on this Website or the completeness or accuracy of such information. 

**30\. RIGHT OF nabbesh S.A.L (offshore) TO INFORMATION ON THIS WEBSITE?**

The information contained on the nabbesh website may not be copied, transmitted, amended or reproduced in any form whatsoever without the prior written consent of nabbesh S.A.L (offshore).?We place paramount importance on customer service and aim to meet your expectations on every occasion. To achieve this aim we need accurate personal information about you. Please help us take prompt and efficient action by updating your User Profile to reflect changes to your personal circumstances. 

**31\. DISPUTES**

You will resolve any claim, cause of action or dispute ("claim") you have with us arising out of or relating to this Statement or nabbesh exclusively in Lebanon in an Lebanese Court. The laws of the Republic of Lebanon will govern this Statement, as well as any claim that might arise between you and us, without regard to conflict of law provisions. You agree to submit to the personal jurisdiction of the courts located in the Republic of Lebanon for the purpose of litigating all such claims.   
If anyone brings a claim against us related to your actions, content or information on nabbesh, you will indemnify and hold us harmless from and against all damages, losses, and expenses of any kind (including reasonable legal fees and costs) related to such claim. 

**32\. OTHER**

This document makes up the entire agreement between the parties regarding nabbesh, and supersedes any prior agreements.   
If any portion of this document is found to be unenforceable, the remaining portion will remain in full force and effect.   
If we fail to enforce any of this Statement, it will not be considered a waiver.   
Any amendment to or waiver of this Statement must be made in writing and signed by us.   
You will not transfer any of your rights or obligations under this Statement to anyone else without our consent.   
All of our rights and obligations under this Statement are freely assignable by us in connection with a merger, acquisition, or sale of assets, or by operation of law or otherwise.   
Nothing in this Statement shall prevent us from complying with the law.   
This Statement does not confer any third party beneficiary rights. 

**33\. COMPANY REGISTRATION DETAILS?**

nabbesh S.A.L (offshore) is a Company incorporated in the Republic of Lebanon with Company registered office address of Plot 347, Unit 22, Block A, Antelias, Lebanon. 

Privacy Policy

nabbesh Privacy Policy is designed to help you understand how we collect and use the personal information you consent to share and help you make informed decisions when using nabbesh, located at www.nabbesh.com By using or accessing nabbesh, you are accepting the practices described in this Privacy Policy.  
nabbesh collects personal information in the form of a Homepage. The User consents to upload and create a Homepage with nabbesh. The User also consents to having the Homepage accessible and available to all. We will share your personal information with third parties only in the ways that are described in this privacy statement. We do not sell your personal information to third parties. 

**1\. INFORMATION THAT WE COLLECT AND HOW WE USE IT**

  1. We collect information on Users in order to facilitate the operation of the nabbesh Platform. 
  2. The User consents and knowingly chooses to disclose all information that is uploaded to the nabbesh Platform in the form of a Homepage. When you add to your Homepage with further information about yourself, you agree that any registration information you give to nabbesh will always be accurate, correct and up to date. 
  3. The nabbesh Search Facility is available to all Users. Users are also invited to enter personal information which provides an enhanced set of search results. 
    1. When you sign up for a nabbesh Account (or 'Homepage') or other nabbesh services or promotions that require registration, we ask you for personal information such as name and email address. After you have created your Homepage we provide you with the option to add additional personal information such as phone number. We may combine the information that you submit under your Homepage with information from other nabbesh, in order to provide you with a better experience and to improve the quality of our services or to suggest to you people you might know, or other people who may have skills or hobbies of interest to you. For certain information, we give you the opportunity to opt out of combining such information within your account settings page. 
    2. nabbesh provides an invitation service when you register with the Platform. If you choose (consent or opt in) to use our invitation service to tell a contact about our site, we will ask you for information needed to send the invitation, such as your contact's email address or we will ask you to consent to having your contact list(s) imported. We will send your contacts an email in your name inviting him or her to visit the site, and we will send additional reminders. nabbesh stores this information to send invitations and reminders, to register a contact connection if your invitation is accepted, to allow you to see invitations you have sent and to track the success of our referral program. All information that you enter or upload about your contacts will be covered by the same terms of this privacy policy as cover your own information. nabbesh also stores this information (imported contacts information) to avoid duplication of contacts and to check when contacts, not invited by the User, join the nabbesh Platform through registration. nabbesh will also store the User's access details in order to synch the contacts whenever the User logs in. 
    3. When you visit nabbesh, we use a third party tracking partner to gather certain information automatically and store it in log files. This information includes internet protocol (IP) addresses, browser type, internet service provider (ISP), referring/exit pages, operating system, date/time stamp and clickstream data. We use this information, which does not identify individual users, to analyze trends, to administer the site, to track users' movements around the site and to gather demographic information about our user base as a whole. 
    4. In addition, we store certain information from your browser using 'cookies'. A cookie is a piece of data stored on the User's computer tied to information about the User. We send cookies to your computer or other device that uniquely identifies your browser. We use session ID cookies to confirm that Users are logged in. These cookies terminate once the User closes the browser. By default, we use a persistent cookie that stores your login ID (but not your password) to make it easier for you to login when you come back to nabbesh. You can remove or block this cookie using the settings in your browser if you want to disable this convenience feature. We use cookies to collect information about visitors' use of the nabbesh website. The information collected by cookies enables nabbesh to understand the use of its site. This in turn helps to provide visitors with a better experience. nabbesh will not attempt to personally identify visitors from their IP addresses. We use cookies to improve the quality of our service, including storing of User preferences, improving search results and ad selection and tracking User trends, such as how people search. nabbesh also uses cookies in its advertising services to help advertisers and publishers serve and manage ads across the web. We may set one or more cookies in your browser when you visit a website, including nabbesh sites that use our advertising cookies and that view or click an ad supported by nabbesh's advertising services. The use of cookies by our service providers is not covered by our privacy statement. We do not have access or control over these cookies. Our service providers use session ID cookies. 
    5. Our third party service providers use a software technology called clear gifs (a.k.a. Web Beacons/Web Bugs), that help us better manage content on our site by informing us what content is effective. Clear gifs are tiny graphics with a unique identifier, similar in function to cookies and are used to track the online movements of Web users. In contrast to cookies, which are stored on a user's computer hard drive, clear gifs are embedded invisibly on Web pages and are about the size of the period at the end of this sentence. We do not tie the information gathered by clear gifs to our customers' personally identifiable information. 
    6. When you use nabbesh, you may set up your Homepage, form community networks, send messages, perform searches and queries, set up events, add applications, transmit information through various channels and send emails or other communications to nabbesh. We collect the personal information as outlined above so that we can provide you the service and offer personalized features. In most cases, we retain it so that, for instance, you can return to view prior messages you have sent or easily see your community network list. 
    7. Nabbesh have the right to reformat and move Nabbesh, and Homepage information. Nabbesh reserve the right to remove, edit the look and feel of, move or close any Homepage for any reason and to suspend or ban any User Account for any reason. 
    8. Nabbesh may present links in a format that enables us to keep track of whether these links have been followed. We use this information to improve the quality of our search technology, customized content and advertising. 
  4. Any improper collection or misuse of information provided on nabbesh is a violation of the nabbesh Terms and Conditions of Use. 
  5. nabbesh only processes personal information for the purposes described in this Privacy Policy. In addition to the above, such purposes include: 
    1. Providing our services, primarily making nabbesh available to all; 
    2. Providing more relevant search results by utilizing data provided by the User; 
    3. Auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services; 
    4. Ensuring the technical functioning of nabbesh; 
    5. Protecting the rights or property of nabbesh or our Users; and 
    6. Developing new services. 
  6. By using nabbesh, you are consenting to have your personal data transferred to and processed in such jurisdictions as is necessary. 
  7. We provide you the opportunity to participate in surveys on our site. If you participate, we will link certain personally identifiable information provided when you registered for the site to you. Participation in these surveys is completely voluntary and you therefore have a choice whether or not to disclose this information. We use this information to gauge the level of user satisfaction with the site. We use a third party service provider to conduct these surveys. That company is prohibited from using our users' personally identifiable information for any other purpose. We will not share the personally identifiable information you provide through a survey with other third parties unless we give you prior notice and choice. 

**2\. USE OF INFORMATION OBTAINED BY NABBESH**

  1. When you register with nabbesh, you create your own Homepage. We may occasionally use your name and email address to send you notifications regarding new services offered by nabbesh that we think you may find valuable. If you no longer wish to receive these email communications, you may unsubscribe by following the instruction contained in each of the emails you receive. 
  2. Homepage information is used by nabbesh primarily to be presented back to and edited by you when you access the service and to be presented to all. 
  3. The Homepage information that you submit to nabbesh will be available to all Users of the nabbesh Platform. All Homepage information will be available in search results generated for Users and may be made available to third-party search engines. If you no longer wish to have your information indexed you have the option of deleting your Account. People that see your name in searches will be able to access your Homepage information without registering with the nabbesh Platform. If you do not want to be listed in our directory you have the option of deleting your Account. 
  4. Homepage information is used by nabbesh to improve the functionality of the nabbesh Platform. 
  5. nabbesh may send you service-related announcements from time to time through the general operation of the service. 
  6. nabbesh reserves the right to send you notices about your Account even if you opt out of all voluntary email notifications. 
  7. nabbesh may use information in your Homepage without identifying you as an individual to third parties. We do this for purposes such as aggregating how many people are in a network like a group of electricians, and also personalizing advertisements and promotions so that we can provide you with up to date nabbesh promotions and sponsors of community groupings. We believe this benefits you. Where such information is used, we generally allow you to specify in your User Account Settings that you do not want this to be done or to take other actions that limit the connection of this information to your Homepage (e.g. removing photo tag links). 

**3\. CHILDREN AGED UNDER 12H**

nabbesh does not knowingly collect or solicit personal information from anyone under the age of 12 or knowingly allow such persons to register. If you are under 12, please do not attempt to register for nabbesh or send any personal information about yourself to us (including your name, address, telephone number or email address). No one under the age of 12 may provide any personal information to nabbesh on the nabbesh Platform. In the event that we learn that we have collected personal information from a child under the age of 12 without verification of parental consent, we will delete that information. 

**4\. CHILDREN BETWEEN THE AGES OF 12 AND 18?**

We recommend that children 12 years of age or older ask their parents for permission before sending any information about themselves to anyone over the Internet. 

**5\. SHARING YOUR INFORMATION WITH THIRD PARTIES**

  1. nabbesh is about sharing catalogued skill & hobby information with Users. We share your information with third parties only in limited circumstances where we believe such sharing is (1) reasonably necessary to offer the service, (2) legally required or (3) permitted by you. 
  2. We may provide information to service providers such as an email service provider to send out emails on our behalf, an author management service to provide you with our blog and a customer support service to gather feedback and assist you with questions to help us bring you the services we offer. Specifically, we may use third parties to facilitate our business. In connection with these offerings and business operations, our service providers may have access to your personal information for use for a limited time in connection with these business activities. Where we utilize third parties for the processing of any personal information, we implement reasonable contractual and technical protections limiting the use of that information to the nabbesh-specified purposes. This site uses various analytics services to monitor and improve the quality and usability of the nabbesh Platform. 
  3. We may be required to disclose User information pursuant to lawful requests, such as subpoenas or court orders, or in compliance with applicable laws. We do not reveal information until we have a good faith belief that an information request by law enforcement or private litigants meets applicable legal standards. Additionally, we may share Account or other information when we believe it is necessary to comply with law, to protect our interests or property, to prevent fraud or other illegal activity perpetrated through the nabbesh service or using the nabbesh name, or to prevent imminent bodily harm. This may include sharing information with other companies, lawyers, agents or government agencies. 
  4. If nabbesh becomes involved in a merger, acquisition or any form of sale of some or all of its assets, your personally identifiable information will likely be among the assets transferred. You will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site for 30 days of any such change in ownership or control of your personal information. You can share your nabbesh information with outside applications and websites such as Facebook to make your experiences on those applications and websites better and more commercial. 
  5. We are not responsible for any third party applications and websites that you interact with through the nabbesh Platform. 
  6. If you log in to nabbesh using one of these application's or website's sign-in services and connect with your nabbesh Account, that application or website can access information on nabbesh related to you and your contacts and generate and publish stories about actions you take on that application or website without any additional permission. An application or website that you connect with can generally access the same information that you can see about yourself and your contacts, and an application or website that your contacts connect with can access the same information about you that the contacts can see. 
  7. You can report any suspected misuse of the nabbesh Platform to us, and we will investigate the claim and take appropriate action. 
  8. If the ownership of all or substantially all of the nabbesh business, or individual business units owned by nabbesh S.A.L (offshore), were to change, your User information may be transferred to the new owner so the service can continue operations. In any such transfer of information, you will be notified via email and/or a prominent notice on our Web site of any change in ownership or uses of your personal information, as well as any choices you may have regarding your personal information. 
  9. All sharing of information is done at your own risk. 

**6\. LINKS?**

nabbesh may contain links to other websites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of other websites. We encourage our Users to be aware when they leave our site that they should read the privacy documents of each and every website that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information collected by nabbesh. 

**7\. CHANGING OR REMOVING INFORMATION?**

Access and control over most personal information on nabbesh is readily available through the User Account editing tools. nabbesh Users may modify or delete any of their Account information at any time by logging into their Account. Individuals who wish to delete their nabbesh Account may do so through your User Account Settings. Removed information may persist in back-up copies for a reasonable period of time but will not be generally available to Users of nabbesh. ?We will retain your information for as long as your Account is active or as needed to provide you services. We will retain and use your information as necessary to comply with our legal obligations, resolve disputes and enforce our agreements. ?If you wish to request the deletion of an unauthorized profile, you may do so by emailing us at contact@nabbesh.com. ?If you wish to update your privacy settings you may do so by going to the User Account Settings tab in your account center after logging into your account. ?Where you make use of the communication features of the service to share information with other individuals on nabbesh, however, (e.g. sending a personal message to another nabbesh User) you generally cannot remove such communications. 

**8\. SECURITY?**

nabbesh takes appropriate precautions to protect our Users' information. We follow generally accepted standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. Your Account information is located on a secure server behind a firewall. Therefore, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can contact us at contact@nabbesh.com. 

**9\. TERMS AND CONDITIONS OF USE, NOTICES AND REVISIONS?**

Your use of nabbesh, and any disputes arising from it, is subject to this Privacy Policy as well as our Terms and Conditions of Use and all of its dispute resolution provisions including limitation on damages and choice of law. We reserve the right to change our Privacy Policy and our Terms and Conditions of Use at any time. Changes and clarifications will take effect immediately upon their posting on this site. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email or through notice on the nabbesh website prior to the changes becoming effective. We encourage you to refer to this policy on an ongoing basis so that you understand our current privacy policy. Unless stated otherwise, our current privacy policy applies to all information that we have about you and your Account. 

**10\. CHOICES FOR PERSONAL INFORMATION**

  1. When you sign up to create an Account, this requires registration and we ask you to provide personal information. If we use this information in a manner different from the purpose for which it was collected, then we will ask for your consent prior to such use. 
  2. If we propose to use personal information for any purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the specific service privacy notices, we will offer you an effective way to opt out of the use of personal information for those other purposes. We will not collect or use sensitive information for purposes other than those described in this Privacy Policy and/or in the supplementary service privacy notices, unless we have obtained your prior consent. 
  3. Most browsers are initially set up to accept cookies, but you can reset your browser to refuse all cookies or to indicate when a cookie is being sent. However, some nabbesh features and services may not function properly if your cookies are disabled. 

**11\. DATA INTEGRITY?**

nabbesh processes personal information only for the purposes for which it was collected and in accordance with this Privacy Policy or any applicable service-specific privacy notice. We review our data collection, storage and processing practices to ensure that we only collect, store and process the personal information needed to provide or improve our services or as otherwise permitted under this Policy. We take reasonable steps to ensure that the personal information that we process is accurate, complete and current, but we depend on our Users to update or correct their personal information whenever necessary. 

**12\. PRIVACY MATTERS?**

When we receive formal written or emailed complaints it is nabbesh's policy to contact the complaining User regarding his or her concerns. We will cooperate with the appropriate regulatory authorities, including local data protection authorities, to resolve any complaints regarding the transfer of personal data that cannot be resolved between nabbesh and an individual. 

|
